{
    "subject": "resource/Koki_Yonekura",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Chiba_Prefecture",
    "human_readable": "Koki Yonekura was born in Chiba Prefecture.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9390605092048645,
            "question": "Where was Koki Yonekura born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8859221339225769,
            "question": "In what prefecture was Koki Yonekura raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6725014448165894,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Koki Yonekura's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6534594297409058,
            "question": "What is Koki Yonekura known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5628829598426819,
            "question": "Is there any information about Koki Yonekura's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5355669260025024,
            "question": "Are there any notable people from Chiba Prefecture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48898693919181824,
            "question": "Where might Koki Yonekura live now?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45779091119766235,
            "question": "What is Chiba Prefecture famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43455374240875244,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Koki Yonekura's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4253729581832886,
            "question": "What type of work is Koki Yonekura involved in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Koki Yonekura was born in Chiba Prefecture.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8231_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Koki Yonekura's early life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8231_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Chiba Prefecture famous for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8231_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might Koki Yonekura live now?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8231_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8231_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8231_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8231_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8231_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8231_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8231_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8231_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8231_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8231_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8231_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can answer your question as follows:\n\n{ \"output\": \"no\" }\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while there is a mention of Koki Yonekura's birthplace, it is specifically stated as \"Chiba\", which refers to a city in Japan, not Chiba Prefecture."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states that Koki Yonekura was born in Inage-ku, Chiba. Chiba is a prefecture in Japan, and thus the statement that Koki Yonekura was born in Chiba Prefecture is supported by the documents provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It contradicts with the information provided in context 4, where it is stated that Koki Yonekura was born in Chiba.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}